gabriella-psychic.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Updated 09/01/2010 

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet’s vast array of information and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all end users of our Internet Services and Content.

This Policy also explains what we do with the information we collect and the choices concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

The web site www.gabriella-psychic.com (“site”) provides entertainment and cultural content, related to divinatory readings, astrology themes, numerology, tarot, horoscopes, reports, information, and access to e-mail consultations (“Content”). The Editor of www.gabriella-psychic.com is Gabriella Psychic (“the Editor”).

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") means information that can be directly associated with you (such as your name, email address), or information about activities directly linked to you (such as products that you have licensed or purchased). We collect PII in the following ways:

**1.1 Information that you provide to us directly:**

  * When you contact or communicate with the Editor, we may gather information such as your name and email address;
  * When you participate in a promotional offer (such as a trial subscription) and/or purchase products or Services, we may gather information regarding the offer that you participate in, and any products or Services that you purchase, as well as financial information such as your credit card number.
  * When you register for an online purchase, subscribe to a newsletter, or click on a URL, we may gather user preferences, product interests, other customer profile information

**1.2 Information we collect through online technology**

  * When you are on the Editor websites, we collect information about the pages you visit. Some web pages use cookies to automatically collect information from you. We may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of characters) to your computer to uniquely identify your browser. We may use "web beacons" (electronic images also known as pixel tags or clear gifs) to recognize an Editor cookie on your computer when you view or act upon an Editor web page, an Editor advertisement posted on a third-party web page, or an email from us.
  * Cookies, web beacons and similar technologies enable us to collect information about your visits to our websites, such as: 
    * Internet Protocol Address
    * Browser type
    * Operating system
    * Referring site (site you visited before coming to our site)
    * Date and time of visit
    * URL of pages visited
    * Other browsing behavior, such as products and white papers downloaded

Most browsers allow you to remove and block cookies and web beacons. If you do so, you will need to re-enter your User Name and password to access certain parts of our web sites and you will be served only generic information that is not focused on your specific interests. Also, you may not be able to use certain of the Editor web site features or take full advantage of our offerings.

**2\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We use PII to conduct business, provide information and support for products and Services, improve our understanding of your needs and interests, develop and improve our Services and products, and personalize communications. Examples include:

  * Advising you of relevant promotions, products, Services, and news about the Editor and affiliated third-parties
  * Processing and fulfilling orders 
  * Creating and monitoring accounts 
  * Market research projects 
  * Analyzing how our products and Services are used
  * Personalizing content and advertising 
  * Monitoring our Services in order to prevent and identify unauthorized content use and violations of our end user agreements
  * Planning and forecasting 
  * Legal compliance 
  * Preventing fraud and prohibited or illegal activities

**3\. HOW WE SHARE AND DISCLOSE PII**

We may share or disclose your PII with:

  * Companies that are related to the Editor, in order to support business and marketing processes
  * Our service providers and suppliers, who are acting and using your information solely on our behalf 
  * As necessary, if we suspect a violation of our policies or to protect the rights or safety of any person or entity
  * Government agencies, law enforcement agencies and others, based on a good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary to respond to judicial process, valid government inquiry, or is otherwise required by law
  * The buyer, if the Editor or any of its assets are sold
  * Other third-parties for purposes you have allowed by agreeing to this Policy, or by otherwise giving us your consent
  * Others including without limitation other participants, to the extent of any PII that is posted by you or an authorized third-party to our wikis, forums, blogs, message boards, chat rooms and other social network environments

**4\. NOTICE AND CHOICE**

We provide notice about our use of PII in this Policy, in our web pages, and in other locations where we collect information. You can choose whether or not to provide your PII to us. If you choose not to provide PII, you may be not be able to take advantage of certain offers, options, events and Services that depend upon accurate PII.

If you have chosen to receive personalized messages, newsletters, or promotional communications by e-mail, you can at any time cancel this, or “opt-out”, by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in every e-mail you receive.

You may unsubscribe directly from our site by following this link: <http://www.gabriella-psychic.com/desinscription.php> Put your email in the indicated field, press “Send” and your opt-out will be immediately effective

**5\. ONWARD TRANSFER**

We will only share personal information with third parties if those third parties provide an adequate level of data protection to help ensure the security of personal data.

**6\. SECURITY**

The Editor uses administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect the security, confidentiality and integrity of PII against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. In addition, we use standard security protocols and mechanisms to transmit sensitive data such as credit card details.

**7\. ACCESS AND ACCURACY**

We provide individuals with reasonable access to their PII in order to have it corrected, amended or deleted where it is inaccurate or inappropriate for the specified purposes of processing.

**8\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Policy changes on this page.
